{
  "vocabulary": {
    "beginner": {
      "section1": {
        "sectionDescription": "greetings",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is 'hello'?",
            "word": "salut",
            "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "merci", "salut"],
            "answer": "salut"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "Say 'Good morining' to Rhoda. __ Rhoda!",
            "word": "bonjour",
            "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "salut", "merci"],
            "answer": "bonjour"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is 'goodbye'?",
            "word": "au revoir",
            "options": ["merci", "oui", "au revoir", "salut"],
            "answer": "au revoir"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Select the correct meaning: 'goodnight'?",
            "word": "bonne nuit",
            "options": ["merci", "oui", "au revoir", "bonne nuit"],
            "answer": "bonne nuit"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "What do you hear?",
            "word": "bonsoir",
            "options": ["merci", "bonsoir", "au revoir", "salut"],
            "answer": "bonsoir"
          }
        ]
      },
     "section2": {
        "sectionDescription": "everydayWords",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "yes",
            "word": "oui",
            "options": ["oui", "nuit", "fille", "je"],
            "answer": "oui"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "__ suis Sam!",
            "word": "je",
            "options": ["tu", "nous", "vous", "ils"],
            "answer": "je"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "am",
            "word": "suis",
            "options": ["nous", "suis", "vous", "les"],
            "answer": "suis"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Select the correct meaning: 'no'?",
            "word": "non",
            "options": ["oui", "non", "moi", "jour"],
            "answer": "non"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'maybe'",
            "word": "peut-être",
            "options": ["oui", "non", "moi", "peut-être"],
            "answer": "peut-être"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "intermediate": {
     "section1": {
        "sectionDescription": "greetings",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is 'thank you'?",
            "word": "merci",
            "options": ["bonjour", "oui", "merci", "salut"],
            "answer": "merci"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "Please: 'S'il vous ___",
            "word": "plaît",
            "options": ["rein", "plait", "oui", "non"],
            "answer": "plaît"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is 'nice to meet you'?",
            "word": "enchanté(e)",
            "options": ["merci", "oui", "enchantée", "plait"],
            "answer": "enchanté(e)"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Select the correct meaning: 'welcome'?",
            "word": "bienvenue",
            "options": ["merci", "oui", "enchantée", "bienvenue"],
            "answer": "bienvenue"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "good day",
            "word": "bonne journée",
            "options": ["merci", "bonne journée", "bienvenue", "salut"],
            "answer": "bonne journée"
          }
        ]
      },
     "section2": {
        "sectionDescription": "everydayWords",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "The day",
            "word": "le jour",
            "options": ["le jour", "la nuit", "une fille", "je"],
            "answer": "le jour"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "garçon __ fille.",
            "word": "et",
            "options": ["et", "un", "une", "suis"],
            "answer": "et"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'house'",
            "word": "maison",
            "options": ["jour", "maison", "livre", "école"],
            "answer": "maison"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Select the correct meaning: 'work'?",
            "word": "travail",
            "options": ["maison", "livre", "travail", "jour"],
            "answer": "travail"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'store'",
            "word": "magasin",
            "options": ["magasin", "maison", "livre", "école"],
            "answer": "magasin"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'book'",
            "word": "livre",
            "options": ["magasin", "maison", "livre", "école"],
            "answer": "livre"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'boy'",
            "word": "garçon",
            "options": ["garçon", "fille", "femme", "homme"],
            "answer": "garçon"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'girl'",
            "word": "fille",
            "options": ["garçon", "fille", "femme", "homme"],
            "answer": "fille"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'man'",
            "word": "homme",
            "options": ["garçon", "fille", "femme", "homme"],
            "answer": "homme"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'woman'",
            "word": "femme",
            "options": ["garçon", "fille", "femme", "homme"],
            "answer": "femme"
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "advanced": {
      "section1": {
        "sectionDescription": "greetings",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is 'see you later'?",
            "word": "à plus tard",
            "options": ["à plus tard", "bonne journée", "bienvenue", "salut"],
            "answer": "à plus tard"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "Excuse me Rhoda!. __ Rhoda!",
            "word": "excusez-moi",
            "options": ["à plus tard", "bienvenue", "excusez-moi", "merci"],
            "answer": "excusez-moi"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is 'see you tommorrow'?",
            "word": "à demain",
            "options": ["merci", "bienvenue", "à demain", "à plus tard"],
            "answer": "à demain"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Select the correct meaning: 'journey'?",
            "word": "voyage",
            "options": ["travail", "magasin", "bonne journée", "voyage"],
            "answer": "voyage"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Write it in French, 'safe journey'",
            "word": "bon voyage",
            "options": ["bon nuit", "bonsoir", "travail", "bon voyage"],
            "answer": "bon voyage"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which one of these is a'car'?",
            "word": "voiture",
            "options": ["chat", "chien", "voiture", "tableau"],
            "answer": "voiture"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Weather",
            "word": "temp",
            "options": ["temp", "chien", "voiture", "chat"],
            "answer": "temp"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "to go",
            "word": "aller",
            "options": ["aller", "avoir", "parler", "dire"],
            "answer": "aller"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "to have",
            "word": "avoir",
            "options": ["aller", "avoir", "parler", "dire"],
            "answer": "avoir"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "to say",
            "word": "dire",
            "options": ["aller", "avoir", "parler", "dire"],
            "answer": "dire"
          }

        ]
      },
     "section2": {
        "sectionDescription": "everydayWords",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "To eat",
            "word": "manger",
            "options": ["aller", "manger", "parler", "dire"],
            "answer": "manger"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "__ es Sam!",
            "word": "tu",
            "options": ["tu", "nous", "vous", "ils"],
            "answer": "tu"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'to speak'",
            "word": "parler",
            "options": ["aller", "avoir", "parler", "dire"],
            "answer": "parler"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Select the correct meaning: 'to be'?",
            "word": "être",
            "options": ["être", "avoir", "parler", "dire"],
            "answer": "être"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'to want'",
            "word": "vouloir",
            "options": ["aller", "avoir", "parler", "vouloir"],
            "answer": "vouloir"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "petite",
            "word": "small",
            "options": ["larger", "big", "small", "pretty"],
            "answer": "small"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "bad",
            "word": "mauvais",
            "options": ["petite", "mauvais", "jeune", "bon"],
            "answer": "mauvais"
          },
          
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "young",
            "word": "jeune",
            "options": ["petite", "mauvais", "jeune", "bon"],
            "answer": "jeune"
          },
          
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "beautiful",
            "word": "beau",
            "options": ["beau", "mauvais", "jeune", "viens"],
            "answer": "beau"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "mcq",
            "question": "Which of these is 'the orange'?",
            "word": "orange",
            "options": ["orange", "papaya", "avocado", "pizza"],
            "answer": "orange"
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  },
  "sentenceBuilding": {
    "beginner": {
      "section1": {
        "sectionDescription": "greetings",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "Comment __ va?",
            "sentence": "How are you?",
            "options": ["ce", "ci", "ça", "sa"],
            "answer": "ça"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'I am fine' in French",
            "sentence": "I am fine",
            "options": ["bien", "je", "bien"],
            "answer": "je vais bien"
          }, 
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Construct the sentence: 'What is your name?'",
            "sentence": "What is your name?",
            "options": ["Comment", "tu", "t'appelles", "s'appelle"],
            "answer": "Comment tu t'appelles?"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Construct the sentence: 'My name is Eric'",
            "sentence": "My name is Eric",
            "options": ["m'appelle","Mon", "nom", "Eric", "est"],
            "answer": "Mon nom est ..."
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Construct the sentence: 'I am a boy'",
            "sentence": "I am a boy",
            "options": ["suis", "un","Je", "garçon", "une"],
            "answer": "Je suis un garçon"
          }
        ]
      },
     "section2": {
        "sectionDescription": "everydayWords",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write in English: 'Tu manges une orange'",
            "sentence": "Tu manges une orange",
            "options": ["eating", "an", "orange", "you", "are"],
            "answer": "You are eating an orange"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "chat __ chein?",
            "sentence": "cat and dog",
            "options": ["ce", "et", "est", "sa"],
            "answer": "chat et chein"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write in French: 'Are you a man?'",
            "sentence": "Are you a man?",
            "options": ["fille","Es-tu", "un", "homme"],
            "answer": "Es-tu un homme"
          },
          
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write in English: 'Tu es un chien'",
            "sentence": "Tu es un chien",
            "options": [ "a", "dog", "You", "are"],
            "answer": "You are a dog"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": " __ homme ____ femme",
            "sentence": "a man and a woman",
            "options": ["un", "une", "et", "sa"],
            "answer": "un et une"
          }
          
        ]
      }
    },
    "intermediate": {
      "section1": {
        "sectionDescription": "greetings",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "__ rien",
            "sentence": "You are welcome",
            "options": ["de", "le", "la", "un"],
            "answer": "de"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "Quel est __ nom?",
            "sentence": "What is your name?",
            "options": ["ton", "mon", "son", "notre"],
            "answer": "ton"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'I am going to the store' in French",
            "sentence": "I am going to the store",
            "options": ["magasin", "au", "je", "vais"],
            "answer": "je vais au magasin"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'This is a book' in French",
            "sentence": "This is a book",
            "options": ["livre", "est", "un", "c'est"],
            "answer": "c'est un livre"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'Une fille mange un croissant' in English",
            "sentence": "Une fille mange un croissant",
            "options": ["girl", "croissant", "eating", "a", "is"],
            "answer": "A girl is eating a croissant"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'A woman is eating an orange' in French",
            "sentence": "A woman is eating an orange",
            "options": ["une", "mange", "une", "femme", "orange"],
            "answer": "une femme mange une orange"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'A man and a cat' in French",
            "sentence": "A man and a cat",
            "options": ["un", "chat", "et", "un", "homme"],
            "answer": "un homme et un chat"
          }
        ]
      },
     "section2": {
        "sectionDescription": "everydayWords",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'It's an orange' in French",
            "sentence": "It's an orange",
            "options": ["c'est", "un", "orange", "une"],
            "answer": "c'est une orange"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'It is a school' in French",
            "sentence": "It is a school",
            "options": ["c'est", "un", "école", "une"],
            "answer": "c'est une école"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'I am going to work' in French",
            "sentence": "I am going to work",
            "options": ["au", "je", "travail", "vais"],
            "answer": "je vais au travail"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'We are coming home' in French",
            "sentence": "We are coming home",
            "options": ["maison", "nous", "venons", "à"],
            "answer": "nous venons à la maison"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'a handsome boy' in French",
            "sentence": "a handsome boy",
            "options": ["beau", "un", "garçon", "jeune"],
            "answer": "un garçon beau"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'a beautiful girl' in French",
            "sentence": "a beautiful girl",
            "options": ["belle", "une", "fille", "petite"],
            "answer": "une fille belle"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'a big house' in French",
            "sentence": "a big house",
            "options": ["grande", "une", "maison", "garçon"],
            "answer": "une maison grande"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'a small cat' in French",
            "sentence": "a small cat",
            "options": ["petit", "un", "chat", "fille"],
            "answer": "un chat petit"
          }
          
        ]
      }
    },
    "advanced": {
      "section1": {
        "sectionDescription": "greetings",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'The man is a doctor' in French",
            "sentence": "The man is a doctor",
            "options": ["médecin", "L'homme", "est", "un"],
            "answer": "L'homme est un médecin"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'The boy is my friend' in French",
            "sentence": "The boy is my friend",
            "options": ["Le", "garçon", "est", "mon", "ami"],
            "answer": "Le garçon est mon ami"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'I speak French' in French",
            "sentence": "I speak French",
            "options": ["Je", "parle", "français"],
            "answer": "Je parle français"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'She is a teacher' in French",
            "sentence": "She is a teacher",
            "options": ["Elle", "est", "professeur"],
            "answer": "Elle est professeur"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'He is a student' in French",
            "sentence": "He is a student",
            "options": ["garçon","Il", "est", "étudiant"],
            "answer": "Il est étudiant"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'She is a doctor' in French",
            "sentence": "She is a doctor",
            "options": ["Elle", "professeur","est", "médecin"],
            "answer": "Elle est médecin"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'He is a teacher' in French",
            "sentence": "He is a teacher",
            "options": ["Il", "est", "maison","professeur"],
            "answer": "Il est professeur"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'She is a student' in French",
            "sentence": "She is a student",
            "options": ["étudiante", "Elle", "est", "magasin"],
            "answer": "Elle est étudiante"
          },

          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'The book is on the table' in French",
            "sentence": "The book is on the table",
            "options": ["la tableau","Le livre", "est", "sur", "chat"],
            "answer": "Le livre est sur la table"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "je suis ___ femme",
            "sentence": "Je suis une femme",
            "options": ["moi", "un", "une", "et"],
            "answer": "une"
          }  
          
        ]
      },
     "section2": {
        "sectionDescription": "everydayWords",
        "questions": [
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "__ est ma sœur",
            "sentence": "Elle est ma sœur",
            "options": ["Elle", "Il", "Nous", "Vous"],
            "answer": "Elle"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "__ sommes une famille",
            "sentence": "Nous sommes une famille",
            "options": ["Nous", "Vous", "Ils", "Je"],
            "answer": "Nous"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'I want coke and pizza' in French",
            "sentence": "I want coke and pie",
            "options": ["Je", "et", "pizza", "veux", "coca"],
            "answer": "Je veux coca et pizza"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'I am hungry' in French",
            "sentence": "I am hungry",
            "options": ["je", "affamé", "suis", "très"],
            "answer": "Je suis affamé"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "I eat everyday: Je __ chaque jour",
            "sentence": "I eat every day",
            "options": ["mange", "bois", "regarde", "écoute"],
            "answer": "mange"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "Le temps est __",
            "sentence": "The weather is good",
            "options": ["bon", "mauvais", "chaud", "froid"],
            "answer": "bon"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "The car is orange: La __ est orange",
            "sentence": "The car is orange",
            "options": ["voiture", "maison", "arbre", "chat"],
            "answer": "voiture"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "fill-in",
            "question": "Je __ être infirmière",
            "sentence": "I want to be a nurse",
            "options": ["veux", "suis", "ai", "fais"],
            "answer": "veux"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'My brother is a carpenter' in French",
            "sentence": "My brother is a carpenter",
            "options": ["charpentier", "un", "est", "frère", "mon"],
            "answer": "Mon frère est un charpentier"
          },
          {
            "questionType": "construct-sentence",
            "question": "Write 'I love oranges' in French",
            "sentence": "I love oranges",
            "options": ["oranges", "j'", "aime", "les"],
            "answer": "J'aime les oranges"
          }
          
          
          
          
          
          
          
          
          
          
        ]
      }
    }

  },

  "dialogueSimulation": {
    "beginner": {
      "section1": {
        "sectionDescription": "greetings",
        "questions": [
          
        ]
      },
     "section2": {
        "sectionDescription": "everydayWords",
        "questions": [
         
        ]
      }
    },
    "intermediate": {
      "section1": {
        "sectionDescription": "greetings",
        "questions": [
          
        ]
      },
     "section2": {
        "sectionDescription": "everydayWords",
        "questions": [
         
        ]
      }
    },
    "advanced": {
      "section1": {
        "sectionDescription": "greetings",
        "questions": [
          
        ]
      },
     "section2": {
        "sectionDescription": "everydayWords",
        "questions": [
         
        ]
      }
    }
  }
}
